<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><head><title>Independent Financial Advisor, Financial Planner and Investment Advisor</title>

</head><meta content="financial advisors, independent financial advisor, independent financial adviser, financial advisor, financial planner" name="Keywords"/><meta content="Dan Goldie is an independent financial advisor, financial planner and investment advisor." name="Description"/><meta content="text/html; charset=utf-8" http-equiv="Content-Type"/><body class="twoColFixLtHdr"><div id="sh1"><div id="”sh2″"><div id="”sh3″"><div id="”sh4″"><div id="”sh5″"><div id="”sh6″"><div id="”sh7″"><div id="”sh8″"><div id="container"><div id="HeaderLinks"><a href="contactUs.html">Contact Us</a> | <a href="directions.html">Locate Us</a></div>
<div id="header"><h1>&#160;</h1>
</div><div id="sidebar1"><div id="MenuBar"><ul><li><a href="index.html">Home</a></li>
<li><a href="why_DGFS.html">The DGFS Difference</a></li>
<li><a href="wealth.html">Wealth Management</a></li>
<li><a href="investment.html">Investment Management</a></li>
<li><a href="partners.html">Our Partners</a></li>
<li><a href="aboutUs.html">About Us</a></li>
<li><a href="companyNews.html">Company News</a></li>
<li><a href="ClientPage.html">Client Resources</a></li>
</ul></div>
<p><STREET>750 Menlo Avenue
<br/>Suite 200</STREET>
<br/><CITY>Menlo Park</CITY>, <STATE>CA</STATE> <ZIPCODE>94025</ZIPCODE>
<br/><TEL>(650) 566-1121</TEL> phone
<br/><FAX>(650) 566-1122</FAX> fax
<br/><a id="email" href="mailto:dan@dangoldie.com"><EMAIL>dan@dangoldie.com</EMAIL></a>
</p><br/>
</div><div id="mainContent"><div class="photo"><img id="Photo" height="254" src="Images/experienced.jpg" alt="Dan Goldie Financial Services - About Us" width="699" name="Photo"/><h1 class="twoColFixLtHdr"><img class="twoColFixLtHdr" height="32" src="Images/AboutUs.png" alt="About Dan Goldie Financial Services - An independent financial advisor and financial planner" width="660"/></h1></div><h1 class="twoColFixLtHdr"><PER>Daniel C. Goldie</PER>, CFA, CFP
<br/>President</h1>

<p><img id="BioPhoto" height="158" src="Images/Goldie_retouched.jpg" alt="Daniel C. Goldie, CFA, CFP, President" width="150" name="BioPhoto"/><PER>Dan Goldie</PER> is the President and Founder of <ORG>Dan Goldie Financial Services</ORG>. He is a fee-only, independent financial advisor and financial planner. For nearly two decades he has devoted his professional career to helping individual investors and their families realize their investment and financial goals.
<br/>
<br/>Dan is the trusted advisor to a diverse group of individuals and families, including business executives, attorneys, physicians, engineers, professors, retirees, former professional athletes, and many others. His clients are located in the San Francisco Bay Area and across the United States.
<br/>
<br/>He has built his advisory business by combining a sound asset class investing methodology with holistic financial planning and first-class client service. Dan has co-authored two investment books: <span id="italics">The Prudent Investor&apos;s Guide to Beating the Market at Its Own Game</span> published by McGraw-Hill in 1998, and the #1 national bestseller, <span id="italics"><a href="http://www.theinvestmentanswerbook.com">The Investment Answer: Learn to Manage Your Money &amp; Protect Your Financial Future</a></span> published by Business Plus (Hachette Book Group) in 2011.
<br/>
<br/>Jargon-free and written for all investors—experienced, beginner, and everyone in between— <span id="italics">The Investment Answer</span> distills the process into five straightforward decisions that can lead to safe and sound ways to manage your money. The inspirational story behind the book and its message has attracted national media attention and inspired thousands to change the way they save and invest.
<br/>
<br/>A former NCAA singles champion for Stanford University, Goldie began his investment career as an independent financial advisor in 1991 after retiring from the men&apos;s professional tennis tour, where he was ranked as high as 27th in the world and was a Wimbledon quarterfinalist.
<br/>
<br/>Today, Goldie is one of the leading independent advisors in the wealth management industry and a #1 New York Times bestselling author. He has been recognized by the San Francisco Business Times as one of the top 25 Bay Area independent advisors, and by Barron&apos;s Magazine as one of the top 100 independent financial advisors in the United States. Goldie&apos;s media appearances include ABC News, Fox Business News, National Public Radio, Yahoo! Finance, and CBS Moneywatch, and he has been quoted in the New York Times, Wall Street Journal, San Jose Mercury News, San Francisco Examiner, and many other business and financial publications.
<br/>
<br/>Dan holds an A.B. in economics from <ORG>Stanford University</ORG> and an M.B.A. from the <ORG>Walter A. Haas School of Business</ORG>, at the <ORG>University of California</ORG> at Berkeley. He is a member of the <ORG>CFA Institute</ORG> and the <ORG>CFA Society of San Francisco</ORG> and has earned the Chartered Financial Analyst designation, and is a CERTIFIED FINANCIAL PLANNER™ certificant.
<br/>
<br/><strong>Interested in booking <PER>Dan Goldie</PER> to speak at your next event?</strong>
<br/>Contact <PER>Steve Sobel</PER> with <ORG>Washington Speakers Bureau</ORG> at <TEL>703.684.0555</TEL> or <a href="mailto:SteveS@WashingtonSpeakers.com"><EMAIL>SteveS@WashingtonSpeakers.com</EMAIL></a></p>

<p></p><h1 class="twoColFixLtHdr"><PER>Dirk Gilliard</PER>,
<br/>Partner</h1>

<p><img id="BioPhoto" height="158" src="Images/Dirk_Headshot.jpg" alt="Dirk Gilliard, Partner" width="150" name="BioPhoto"/><PER>Dirk Gilliard</PER> is a Partner of <ORG>Dan Goldie Financial Services</ORG>. He is a fee-only, independent financial advisor and financial planner. For over 15 years, he has been helping individual investors and their families realize their investment goals.
<br/>
<br/>Dirk manages investment portfolios and provides wealth advisory services to business owners, executives, professors, writers, farmers, attorneys and others. With over 20 years of industry experience, he carries with him expertise in many aspects of personal financial planning and wealth management including, asset allocation strategies, stock option planning, real estate and alternative asset consulting, tax management strategies, and insurance planning.
<br/>
<br/>Prior to joining <ORG>Dan Goldie Financial Services</ORG>, Dirk ran his own investment firm, <ORG>Gilliard Capital Management</ORG>, based in <CITY>Marin County</CITY>, <STATE>California</STATE>. Prior to that, he served as Principal with <ORG>Private Capital Management, Inc.</ORG> Dirk also worked as Principal with <ORG>Emeritus Investment Management, Inc.</ORG>, and as a financial advisor with Morgan Stanley/Dean Witter.
<br/>
<br/>Dirk holds a B.A. degree in political economy of industrial societies from <ORG>University of California</ORG> at Berkeley, where he was a member of the men&apos;s water polo team. He currently serves as the Chair for the Investment Committee for the <ORG>Redwood Foundation</ORG> as well as serving on the finance committee for the San Francisco Board of Advisors to the Salvation Army. Once a competitive age-group triathlete, Dirk now spends most of his free time raising his two young sons with his wife of 6 years.
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
</p><br/>
</div><div id="footer"><p>Investment Advisory Services Provided through <ORG>Dan Goldie Financial Services LLC</ORG>, a Registered Investment Advisor
<br/><a href="Images/Privacy.pdf">Privacy Policy</a> | <a href="legal.html">Legal Notice</a> &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#169; 2011 <ORG>Dan Goldie Financial Services LLC</ORG></p>
</div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div></div><div id="email_tooltip" class="tooltipContent">
<p><a href="mailto:dan@dangoldie.com"><img src="Images/Email.jpg" height="30" alt="Send E-mail to Dan Goldie" width="63"/></a></p><p><a href="mailto:dan@dangoldie.com">Click to send</a></p>

<p><a href="mailto:dan@dangoldie.com">e-mail to <PER>Dan Goldie</PER>.</a></p>
</div></body><noscript><img src="http://rt.trafficfacts.com/ns.php?k=15249g38bc91fc4aea4c1d8cac1541ce42c9936bc31cd3h6" height="1" alt="" width="1"/><noscript><div class="statcounter"><a target="_blank" title="wordpress visitor" href="http://www.statcounter.com/wordpress.org/"><img class="statcounter" alt="wordpress visitor" src="http://c.statcounter.com/5164758/0/3751c354/1/"/></a></div></noscript></noscript></html>